there is perhaps
也许有
no single geographic feature
没有单一的地理特征
that has advanced the American economy
推动了美国经济的发展
more than the Mississippi River
超过密西西比河
that's because
那是因为
nowhere else on earth has a river been crafted
地球上没有其他地方有河流
into this long
变成这么长
of a navigable
可通航的
commercial waterway
商业航道
nowhere else can one float a barge 1800 miles or
没有其他地方可以让驳船漂浮1800英里或
2900 kilometers down a river
顺流而下2900公里
without encountering one stretch of low water
没有遇到一片低潮
one bout of rapids one rock in the way
一阵急流，一块石头挡住了去路
one single obstacle to seamless commercial navigation
无缝商业导航的一个障碍
and compounding this waterway supremacy
加剧了航道霸权
is its tributaries
是它的支流
The Tennessee River extends
田纳西河延伸
navigability as far as Knoxville
远至诺克斯维尔的通航能力
the Arkansas as far as Tulsa
从阿肯色州一直到塔尔萨
the Missouri to Sioux City Illinois to Chicago
密苏里州到伊利诺伊州苏城再到芝加哥
and the Ohio extends
俄亥俄州延伸
almost 1,000 river miles from the Mississippi
距离密西西比河近1000英里
connecting Pittsburgh
连接匹兹堡
to all the rest of the Mississippi River region
密西西比河的其他地区
the simple fact that goods from Pittsburgh
匹兹堡的货物
or Minneapolis or Omaha
或者明尼阿波利斯或者奥马哈
or anywhere else on this map can be transported
或者地图上的其他任何地方都可以运输
exclusively by barge as far as New Orleans
只靠驳船远达新奥尔良
then transferred onto ocean going vessels bound for
然后转移到远洋船只上
anywhere cannot be overstated
任何地方都不能夸大
trucks can move a ton of cargo about
卡车可以运送一吨货物
145 miles with a gallon of fuel
用一加仑燃料行驶145英里
trains and the reduced friction borne
火车和减少的摩擦
out of steel on steel contact
钢接触断钢
extend that gallon to 477 miles
把那加仑油加到477英里
the vessels used on the Mississippi
密西西比号上使用的船只
are able to transport that same tonnage as far as
能够运输同样的吨位
647 miles on a gallon of fuel
一加仑燃料能跑647英里
and the cost differential
和成本差异
is even greater than the efficiency one
甚至比效率更高
due to scale
由于规模
a single barge equals the capacity of 35 railcars or
一艘驳船等于35节轨道车的容量或
134 trucks but a single tug can push upwards of 30
134辆卡车，但一辆拖船可以推进30辆以上
sometimes even
有时甚至
40 barges leading to tremendous economies of scale
40艘驳船带来巨大的规模经济
by one estimate
据估计
while trucks cost an average of five dollars and
而卡车平均成本为5美元
thirty five cents per ton per mile
每吨每英里三十五美分
and trains two dollars and fifty
火车两美元五十
three cents
三美分
tugs transport that same ton a mile at a cost of just
拖船一英里运输同样的吨，成本仅为
97 cents
97美分
the friction of distance just works differently
距离的摩擦作用不同
in the United States
在美国
especially because
尤其是因为
beyond the Mississippi and its tributaries
越过密西西比河及其支流
there's still the entire Great Lake system
还有整个大湖系统
The Sioux Locks in Saltwater
盐水中的苏人船闸
Michigan allow for navigation from Lake Superior
密歇根州允许从苏必利尔湖航行
to the rest of the Great Lakes
去五大湖的其他地方
by some measures
按某些标准
these are America's most important lofts
这些是美国最重要的阁楼
as nearly 100 percent of the country's iron
该国近100%的铁
ore pellets pass through them
矿石颗粒通过它们
on their way to lakeside
在去湖边的路上
processing plants in Indiana and Ohio
在印第安纳和俄亥俄州的加工厂
but if not carrying iron
但如果不携带铁
a vessel from Duluth can float through Lake Huron
一艘来自德卢斯的船可以漂浮在休伦湖
then Erie then take this Canadian canal system
然后是伊利，然后是加拿大的运河系统
that bypasses the impassable Niagara Falls
绕过无法通行的尼亚加拉大瀑布
then make its way through the ST Lawrence Seaway
然后穿过圣劳伦斯航道
system to access the Atlantic Ocean
进入大西洋的系统
add on the Columbia River in the Pacific Northwest
加在太平洋西北部的哥伦比亚河上
connecting inland ports as far as Idaho to the ocean
连接内陆港口远至爱达荷州与海洋
the Sacramento Deepwater Ship Canal
萨克拉门托深水运河
connecting California's capital to San Francisco Bay
连接加州首府和旧金山湾
the Hudson River
哈德逊河
extending navigability through New York State
扩展纽约州的通航能力
and a few others
还有其他几个
the US boasts over 12,000 miles
美国拥有超过12000英里
or
或者
19,000 km of commercially navigable inland waterways
19 000公里商业通航内陆水道
that's a longer transportation system
那是一个更长的运输系统
than the entire rail network of the United Kingdom
比整个英国铁路网还要多
but perhaps the
但也许
greatest indicator
最大指示器
of just how important America's inland waterways are
美国内陆水道的重要性
is
是
how involved the federal government is in running them
联邦政府有多参与管理他们
DC doesn't really run transportation systems
DC并不管理交通系统
the rails are almost entirely privately owned
铁轨几乎完全是私人所有
airports are primarily handled by local governments
机场主要由地方政府管理
even interstates
甚至州际公路
the federal network of highways
联邦公路网
are just funded by DC
只是由DC资助的
but actually owned and run by the states themselves
但实际上是由各州自己拥有和经营的
the Mississippi and these other navigable
密西西比河和其他可航行的
inland waterways
内河航道
are a rare example of the federal government
是联邦政府的罕见例子
actually running a transportation system
实际上运行一个交通系统
on a day to day basis
日复一日
specifically and perhaps bizarrely
具体地说，也许很奇怪
it's a branch of the army
这是军队的一个分支
the Army Corps of engineers
陆军工兵部队
that's responsible for keeping cargo on the river
负责把货物留在河上
running they build and run the locks
运行他们构建和运行锁
they dredge it and bolster its banks
他们疏浚河道加固河岸
and they're allocated over $1 billion a year to do it
他们每年的拨款超过10亿美元
and it's these locks that have
正是这些锁
quite literally
字面意思
kept the American agricultural industry alive
维持了美国的农业
Brazil and the US for example
以巴西和美国为例
are the world's first and second
是世界第一和第二
largest soybean exporters respectively
最大的大豆出口国
tightly competing with each other
相互竞争
to sell massive volumes of the crop to massive
将大量作物出售给大量
faraway buyers
远方买家
like China but it's remarkable that the US
比如中国，但值得注意的是，美国
with a GDP per capita eight times that of Brazil
人均GDP是巴西的八倍
is
是
able to meaningfully compete in a global marketplace
能够在全球市场上有意义地竞争
for a commodity
为了一件商品
where the only thing that matters to a buyer is cost
对买家来说唯一重要的是成本
but in Brazil
但在巴西
the majority of soybean is brought from farms
大部分大豆来自农场
to ocean ports
到海港
by trucks with most of the rest transported by train
用卡车，其余大部分用火车运输
both far costlier than barges
都比驳船贵得多
only a tiny portion is transported by water
只有很小一部分是通过水运输的
as Brazil
作为巴西
just does not have the inland waterway infrastructure
只是没有内河航道基础设施
that the US does
美国这样做
most years
大多数年份
the cost of getting soybean from Brazil to China
从巴西到中国的大豆成本
for example is far higher than that of the US
比如远远高于美国
sometimes as much as double
有时高达两倍
US producers can therefore
因此，美国生产商可以
accept higher production costs
接受更高的生产成本
since
自从
all they have to do is get their product to a river
他们所要做的就是把他们的产品运到河里
and from there it can float all the way to Shanghai
从那里它可以一直飘到上海
but before any soy
但在任何大豆之前
chemical or petroleum product
化学或石油产品
is sent to intermingle with the world economy
被送去与世界经济融为一体
it starts in a place like this harbor
它始于像这个港口这样的地方
where highway railway and a river intersect
公路铁路和河流相交的地方
and Trevero's logistics park to back sits
Trevero的物流园区在后面
here goods
这里的货物
whether by belt and elevator or simple front loader
无论是通过皮带和电梯还是简单的前装载机
are poured into a barge operator's standardized
被倒入驳船操作员的标准化
195 foot by 35 foot barge
195英尺乘35英尺驳船
then lashed together with steel cables to another
然后用钢索绑在一起
14 barges
14艘驳船
and pushed out into the river by diesel powered towboat
被柴油动力拖船推进河里
compared to most commercial vessels
与大多数商船相比
crews on these towboats are small
这些拖船上的船员很少
typically less than 10 people composed of a captain
典型的不到10人组成的队长
a pilot a cook and some engineers and deckhands
一个飞行员一个厨师还有一些工程师和水手
almost universally they work six hour on
他们几乎每天工作6个小时
six hour off schedules
六小时休假
non stop for their entire time on board
他们在船上的整个时间都不间断
typically a 28 day stretch
通常是28天
in practice a given deckhand might work from 5
在实践中，给定的水手可能从5开始工作
30 to 11 30 a
30至11 30 a
m then
m然后
attempt to get some sleep before starting work again
在再次开始工作之前尝试睡一会儿
at 5
在5点
30 p m
before an abbreviated overnight
在一个缩写的过夜之前
rest starting at 11 30 p
从11点30分开始休息
m
米
the only crew member that doesn't follow this schedule
唯一不遵守这个时间表的船员
is the cook
是厨师
who will generally prepare meals to be ready
谁一般会准备饭菜准备好
45 or so minutes before and after the 5
5点前后45分钟左右
30 a m 11 30 a m and 5 30 p m
30 a m 11 30 a m和5 30 p m
transitions
过渡
crew facilities are also basic
船员设施也是基本的
outside of bedrooms these boats might have a small gym
在卧室之外，这些船可能有一个小健身房
crew lounge and galley
船员休息室和厨房
but that's about it
但仅此而已
after all when working 12 hours a day
毕竟一天工作12小时
there's really not much time left for anything
真的没有多少时间做任何事情了
but sleeping and eating
但是睡觉和吃饭
and there's plenty that gets done in those 12 hours on
在这12个小时里有很多事情要做
just 16 miles or
只有16英里或者
25 kilometers
25公里
down the river from Trevero's Logistics Park
从Trevero的物流园区顺流而下
sits lock and dam number 12
位于12号锁和大坝
on the Upper Mississippi
在密西西比河上游
there's never more than a couple dozen miles to go
从来没有超过几十英里的路要走
before arriving to a lock
在到达锁之前
and dam tows
和水坝拖车
notify the lockmaster over radio
用无线电通知锁匠
when they're about 30 minutes away
当他们大约30分钟后
which gives the operator time to prepare the lock
这让操作员有时间准备锁
filling it with water
把它装满水
if a boat's approaching from upstream
如果有船从上游靠近
or draining if the opposite toe
或者排水，如果相反的脚趾
captains must approach each lock carefully
舰长必须小心接近每个船闸
tightly
紧紧地
lining up with the wall that marks its approach
与标志着它接近的墙排成一行
after all there's often a current called an outdraft
毕竟，经常有一种叫做流出的水流
pulling from the entrance of the lock towards the dam
从船闸入口拉向大坝
since that's where the water flows
因为那是水流的地方
when the lock is closed
当锁关闭时
getting sucked into this current can
被吸进这个电流罐
and sometimes does prove disastrous
有时确实是灾难性的
it'll trap a toe upstream of the dam
它会困住水坝上游的一个脚趾
and potentially destroy the structure
并可能破坏结构
so captains will often have their
所以船长通常会有他们的
own notes written down based on their
根据他们的笔记写下自己的笔记
own experience through the years
自己多年的经历
reminding them of the particularities of each lock
提醒他们每个锁的特殊性
but upon successful approach
但在成功接近后
a tug pushes its barges into the lock chamber
一艘拖船把它的驳船推进船闸室
or at least half of them
或者至少一半
that's because the Upper Mississippi has 600 foot locks
那是因为密西西比河上游有600英尺的锁
but the standard toe size through this stretch is
但这段时间的标准脚趾尺寸是
15 barges in a
15艘驳船
3x5 configuration
3x5配置
leading to an overall length of about 1,000 feet
总长度约为1000英尺
therefore deck
因此甲板
hands have to spend about half an hour
手要花大约半个小时
splitting their toe in two
把他们的脚趾劈成两半
before the lock master can even close the gates
在锁匠关上大门之前
and start draining the chamber
并开始排空腔室
that takes about another 20 minutes
那还需要20分钟
then
然后
the first half of the tow gets floated out and tied up
拖车的前半部分被漂浮出来并捆绑起来
as the second half
作为下半场
including the tug itself
包括拖船本身
waits another 20 minutes
再等20分钟
for the chamber to fill up with water again
让房间再次充满水
next after another 20 minute draining cycle
接下来是20分钟的排水周期
it takes about an hour
大约需要一个小时
for deckhands to put the toe back together
让水手把脚趾拼起来
leading to a roughly three to four hour process
导致大约三到四个小时的过程
of getting through
通过
each and every lock
每个锁
mats if they're lucky
如果幸运的话，垫子
the locks each operate on a first come
每个锁都是先来的
first served system
先服务制
meaning if there's another vessel going through
意思是如果有另一艘船通过
a tow has to wait up to three to four hours
拖车得等上三到四个小时
before it can go through
在它通过之前
the three to four hour process
三到四个小时的过程
in the peak fall grain export season
在秋季粮食出口旺季
these delays can really compound
这些延误真的会加剧
and limit the throughput of the river
并限制河流的吞吐量
just when it's needed
就在需要的时候
most and it's along this process
大多数，它沿着这个过程
passing lock after lock
通过一个又一个锁
where it becomes impossible to ignore
在那里它变得无法忽视
that the Mississippi
密西西比河
nor the Illinois for that matter nor the Columbia
伊利诺斯州和哥伦比亚州也一样
nor the Upper Danube
也不是多瑙河上游
nor the Lower Nile are strictly rivers anymore
下尼罗河也不再是严格意义上的河流
it's one thing for a river to be deemed navigable
河流可以通航是一回事
in its simplest definition
在其最简单的定义中
to be sailed by ships or boats
用船或小船航行
but
但是
it's another to live up to the haughty standards of
达到傲慢的标准是另一回事
what's navigable to
什么是可航行的
say the Army Corps of engineers
陆军工程兵团说
whose definition hinges
谁的定义取决于
not on the possibility of making it
不是在成功的可能性上
up or down the river
顺流而下
but the continued consistent
但持续一致
reliability of travel
行程可靠性
along the river for the purpose of commerce
沿河贸易
rivers no matter the state country or continent
河流，无论国家或大陆
are just fickle
只是善变
changing shape and course by the season and the year
随着季节和年份改变形状和路线
they're difficult to govern physically and politically
他们在物质上和政治上都很难管理
consider
考虑
just the task of defining what the Mississippi River
只是定义密西西比河的任务
really is at base you could start with this map
真的是在基地，你可以从这张地图开始。
but that wouldn't
但那不会
consider some of its most important tributaries
考虑它的一些最重要的支流
such as these
比如这些
and still this is oversimplified
这仍然过于简单化了。
as supplying a river that on average moves nearly
作为供应一条平均流动几乎
500 thousand cubic feet of water through it
50万立方英尺的水
every single second
每一秒
requires the tributaries of these tributaries
需要这些支流的支流
along with the unseen groundwater
还有看不见的地下水
from across the river's entire basin
从河的整个流域
draining eventually into this cumulative flow
最终排入这个累积流
from this more holistic
从这个更全面的
albeit far from exhaustive view of the river
尽管远非河流的全景
the Mississippi River's
密西西比河的
an assemblage of gravity fed water
重力供水的集合
from
从
41 percent of the lower 48's landmass spread across
下48世纪41%的陆地分布在
32 American states and two Canadian provinces
美国32个州和加拿大两个省
as an amalgamation of precipitation
作为沉淀的混合
spread across thousands of miles
绵延千里
the river's disposition
河流的性质
is defined by its broader basin
由其更广泛的盆地定义
massive rain here for instance
比如说这里的大雨
could lead to flooding along the rivers below
可能导致下面的河流泛滥
as it did in 1927
就像1927年一样
when a swollen Mississippi killed 500 and
当膨胀的密西西比河造成500人死亡
left hundreds of thousands displaced
导致数十万人流离失所
massive earthquakes here
这里有大地震
could fundamentally reshape the river's path
可以从根本上改变河流的路径
as they did in 1811 and 1812
正如他们在1811年和1812年所做的那样
and a low snow year here and a hot
这里有一年的低雪和炎热
dry summer here
这里夏天干燥
could bring flows down to levels so low
会把流量降到这么低的水平
that it threatens green shipping in the fall
它威胁到秋季的绿色航运
as they did in 2012
就像他们在2012年所做的那样
on the inverse
反过来
what a river does provide
河流能提供什么
that an interstate or rail line can't
州际公路或铁路线不能
is the efficiency boost of buoyancy
是浮力的效率提升
and what a river offers that a canal can't
河流所提供的是运河所不能提供的
is the natural plumbing
是天然管道
which
哪个
while not perfectly streamlined nor always dependable
虽然不是完美的流线型，也不总是可靠的
provides a far more advanced starting point
提供了一个更先进的起点
to first turn a river into a navigable waterway
首先将河流变成可通航的水道
capable of powering international commerce
能够推动国际商业
there needs to be a legal framework
需要有一个法律框架
as to who has purview over the river
谁有权过河
in the US beginning in the 1800s
在美国从19世纪开始
as the fledgling federal government scrambled
羽翼未丰的联邦政府手忙脚乱
to create effective
创造有效
efficient means of transportation
高效交通工具
to spur on economic activity
刺激经济活动
the responsibility of turning natural features
转向自然特征的责任
into navigable ones
变成可航行的
fell on the US Army Corps of engineers
落在美国陆军工兵部队身上
on the Mississippi
在密西西比河上
their work began with
他们的工作始于
the designation of the Mississippi River Commission
密西西比河委员会的指定
and the exploratory mission
和探索任务
to figure out how its flows
弄清楚它是如何流动的
could be harnessed
可以被利用
for the purposes of interstate trade
为了州际贸易的目的
first the goal was to provide
首先，目标是提供
from the upper river below
从上游到下
a consistent 4 foot or 13 meter deep channel
一致的4英尺或13米深的通道
as time went on the ask grew
随着时间的推移，要求越来越多
then it was a 45 foot deep channel
然后是一个45英尺深的通道
then a consistent 6 foot deep channel
然后是一致的6英尺深的通道
then finally with the rivers and Harbors Act of 1930
最后通过了1930年的河流和港口法案
a 9 foot or 3 meter deep channel
9英尺或3米深的通道
for the river's upper reaches
为了河流的上游
this meant significant reconfiguration
这意味着重大的重组
split at ST Louis
在圣路易斯分裂
the Mississippi River has two
密西西比河有两条
rather distinct dispositions
性情鲜明
from ST Paul to ST Louis the river moves quicker
从圣保罗到圣路易斯河水流速加快
it's smaller in stature and it's comparatively steep
它体型较小，相对陡峭
dropping 400 feet or 120 meters over
下降400英尺或120米以上
670 miles or 1100 kilometers
670英里或1100公里
or it was now just about wherever
或者它现在几乎在任何地方
you zoom in on this upper section
你放大上面的部分
it looks pretty uniform
看起来很统一
it's wide
它很宽
it's smooth and every couple dozen miles it's damned
它很光滑，每隔几十英里就会被诅咒
these dams and accompanying locks all 27
这些水坝和配套的船闸都是27
aren't for storage or flood control
不是用来储存或防洪的
but for transportation
但对于运输
representing a massive 1930s federal investment
代表了20世纪30年代的巨额联邦投资
in turning a wild river into a consistent canal
把一条狂野的河流变成一条稳定的运河
for the benefit
为了利益
of Midwestern agricultural exporters
中西部农业出口商的数量
upon which the whole region still relies
整个地区仍然依赖它
some 90 years on
大约90年过去了
the Corps of engineers
工程兵团
still maintains and operates these locks
仍然维护和操作这些锁
and in the intermediate decades
在中间的几十年里
they've expanded to account for 192 navigational locks
他们已经扩展到192个导航锁
nationwide the locks end at ST Louis
全国的锁都在圣路易斯
not long after
不久之后
the Mississippi has added the flow of the Illinois
密西西比河增加了伊利诺斯河的流量
and just before it adds the Ohio
就在它添加俄亥俄州之前
and it's here
它就在这里
where the river's character flips
河流的角色在哪里翻转
from Cairo Illinois to Vicksburg Mississippi
从伊利诺伊州的开罗到密西西比州的维克斯堡
the river has only 600
这条河只有600个
miles to travel to the Gulf Coast
前往墨西哥湾沿岸的路程
but with only 300 feet
但只有300英尺
or 100 meters
或者100米
of elevation to drop across that entire stretch
整个路段的海拔下降
the river restlessly meanders across its massive
这条河不安分地蜿蜒流过它巨大的
historical floodplain
历史洪泛区
creating a winding path to the ocean
创造一条通往海洋的曲径
that stretches out to over 1000 miles or
延伸到1000多英里或
1600 kilometers through the lower Mississippi
穿越密西西比河下游1600公里
average
平均
flows are high enough to deem navigational locks
流量足够高，可以认为是导航锁
and dams unnecessary
大坝是不必要的
but with so much water
但是有这么多水
and so many bends along a flat landscape
沿着平坦的风景有这么多弯道
come other challenges for the Corps of engineers
工程师军团面临的其他挑战
if one is to drive along a country road
如果一个人要沿着乡间小路开车
along the lower Mississippi
沿着密西西比河下游
there's a good chance they can't see it
他们很有可能看不到
that it's on the other side of a grassy mound
它在草丘的另一边
if one is to look at the lower Mississippi from above
如果从上面看密西西比河下游
there's a good chance
很有可能
they'll notice that these grassy mounds don't meander
他们会注意到这些草堆并不蜿蜒
like the river
像河流一样
but make unnatural calculated
但使不自然的计算
perfectly straight lines across the landscape
横跨风景的完美直线
these are the over 2000 miles of levee
这些是超过2000英里的堤坝
built primarily by the U
主要由美国建造
S Army Corps of engineers
美国陆军工兵部队
that millions count on
数百万人指望的
to keep the flooding Mississippi
来阻止密西西比的洪水
out of their towns and homes
离开他们的城镇和家园
when it does dump on the upper reaches of the basin
当它倾倒在盆地的上游时
and that barge operators count on
驳船操作员指望的是
to keep the Mississippi
为了保住密西西比河
in a single dependable chain
在一个可靠的链中
all
全部
of course levees while noticeable to the trained eye
当然，堤坝对训练有素的人来说是显而易见的
are easy to miss
很容易错过
the same can be said about locks and dams
锁和水坝也是如此
just relatively low lying structures
只是相对低洼的建筑
spread across
传播
what seems to be a reasonably slow
似乎相当缓慢
and easy to contain section of river
和容易控制的河段
like the structures
喜欢结构
the continued upkeep of the river is easy to overlook
这条河的持续养护很容易被忽视
too dredging after all
毕竟太疏浚了
isn't terribly visible to the outside observer
对外界观察者来说是不可见的
it's moving sand
是移动的沙子
and silt and sediment from a River Bottom
河底的淤泥和沉积物
and yet continue dredging
但仍继续疏浚
to keep the channel at 9 feet deep
将通道保持在9英尺深
from 2014 to 2023 in the Upper Mississippi
从2014年到2023年在上密西西比州
cost on average
平均成本
45 million dollars a year
一年4500万美元
the same goes for revetment
护岸也是如此
the process of stabilizing riverbanks
稳定河岸的过程
with concrete matting
用混凝土垫子
it's difficult to notice unless you put it in
除非你把它放进去，否则很难注意到
and yet the Armor 1
然而盔甲1
a vessel tasked with laying down the matting
负责铺垫的船
to hold the river in place for another 50 years
把这条河再保持50年
cost a reported
成本报告
125 million dollars
1.25亿美元
all that's to say
那就是说
while rightly paraded as a geographic superpower
作为一个地理上的超级大国而理所当然地炫耀
navigable waterways are hardly natural systems
通航水道不是自然系统
they're expensive to maintain
它们的维护成本很高。
hybrids with a heavy human touch
带有浓重人情味的混血儿
and in the case of most around the US
在美国大多数情况下
the critical human additions that make these safe
使这些安全的关键人类添加剂
and reliable for the frailest of barges and towboats
对于最脆弱的驳船和拖船来说是可靠的
are often overlooked
经常被忽视
and getting really old
而且越来越老了
take locks with most being built mid century
以大多数在建的中世纪的锁为例
or the case of those around the Mississippi
或者密西西比河周围的情况
even earlier nearly all have outlived their estimated
甚至更早，几乎所有人都比他们估计的要长寿
50 year expected lifespan
50年预期寿命
while still operational they're increasingly unreliable
虽然还在运行，但它们越来越不可靠
as a 2023 department of transportation report noted
正如2023年交通部的报告所指出的那样
from 2010 to 2020 across 192 lock sites
从2010年到2020年跨越192个锁定站点
while total lockages have declined
虽然总锁定量有所下降
the percentage of vessels delayed
延误船只的百分比
has climbed from the 30s
已经从30年代攀升
into the 50s
进入50年代
more problematic
更有问题的
the average delay tripled in duration from 2010
平均延迟时间比2010年增加了两倍
to 2019
到2019年
and while shipping companies can mitigate problems
虽然航运公司可以缓解问题
when it comes to planned delays
当涉及到计划的延误时
in 2020
在2020年
about a third of all lock delays were unscheduled
大约三分之一的锁定延迟是计划外的
in the American Society of Civil Engineers
在美国土木工程师协会
most recent Infrastructure Report card
最新的基础设施报告卡
inland waterways received a d
内河航道收到货
while noting that
同时注意到
the Army Corps of engineers reports both a 68
陆军工兵部队报告说
billion dollar backlog
十亿美元的积压
on projects that have been approved
在已批准的项目上
but not financed
但没有资金
and 27 billion dollars
270亿美元
annually on funds not received to do
每年未收到资金
annual required maintenance
年度所需维护
making things even more difficult and
让事情变得更加困难
inland rivers even less dependable
内陆河流更不可靠
is less consistent weather
天气不太稳定
and increasingly common and increasingly extreme
越来越普遍越来越极端
weather events
天气事件
the Mississippi has had low water years in 2012 2013
密西西比河在2012年和2013年经历了低水位年
2022 23 and 24 for instance
例如2022年23日和24日
while also massively flooding in 2019
同时2019年也发生了大规模洪水
then there's the fact that fundamentally
还有一个事实，从根本上说
the locks along most American rivers
大多数美国河流的船闸
are just too small to serve today's purposes
太小了，无法满足今天的目的
much discussion is made
讨论很多
over whether the federal government should upgrade
关于联邦政府是否应该升级
the river to 1200 foot locks
到1200英尺的水闸
the size that could allow upper Mississippi toes
可以允许密西西比脚趾上部的尺寸
to make their way through in one cycle
在一个周期内通过
rather than two
而不是两个
this would increase throughput enormously
这将极大地提高吞吐量
the three or more hour process of passing a lock
通过锁的三个或三个多小时的过程
would go by in just 30 or so minutes
会在30分钟左右过去
saving days of time
节省几天的时间
across one Minneapolis to ST Louis journey
穿过明尼阿波利斯到圣路易斯的旅程
delays at the locks waiting for other traffic to clear
等待其他交通疏通的锁延误
would become a thing of the past
将成为过去
and shipping rates might go down
运费可能会下降
allowing an ever
允许永远
so slightly
如此轻微
expanded profit margin for farmers in Illinois
伊利诺伊州农民的利润率扩大
and Iowa and beyond
爱荷华州和更远的地方
and in fact
而事实上
we'll even get to see what this looks like in practice
我们甚至可以在实践中看到这是什么样子
construction is started at Loch 25
25号湖开始施工
just north of ST Louis to build a brand new
就在圣路易斯北部建造一个全新的
1200 foot lock
1200英尺的锁
funding was secured
资金得到保障
as part of the Biden administration's
作为拜登政府的一部分
Infrastructure Act
基础设施法
and construction is expected to be completed
预计将完成建设
sometime in the 2030s
本世纪30年代的某个时候
also the total amount allocated for the project was 732
此外，为该项目分配的总金额为732英镑。
million dollars
百万美元
that's to say
也就是说
upgrading the entire Upper Mississippi's locks
升级整个密西西比河上游的船闸
would possibly be a project rivaling the annual budget
可能是一个与年度预算相媲美的项目
of NASA and it's not like
美国航天局
there's a lot of revenue
有很多收入
that can pay for these upgrades
可以支付这些升级费用
the Mississippi is completely free to use
密西西比河完全可以自由使用
including its locks
包括它的锁
they'll open and close for any vessel
他们会打开和关闭任何船只
commercial or recreational without charging a cent
不收一分钱的商业或娱乐
at least directly
至少是直接的
the federal government does charge a
联邦政府确实收取了
29 cent per gallon tax
每加仑税29美分
on the fuel used by commercial barges
商业驳船使用的燃料
on designated inland waterways
在指定的内河航道上
in most circumstances
在大多数情况下
which goes into a trust fund
然后存入信托基金
that is primarily used for construction projects
主要用于建筑项目
on the waterways
在水道上
rather than operations
而不是操作
so in 2020 for example
例如，在2020年
131 million dollars of the Army Corps of engineering
陆军工程兵团的1.31亿美元
spending on inland waterways
内河航道支出
came from this fund
来自这个基金
but this was out of a total annual cost of 13
但这是每年13英镑的总费用中的一部分。
billion dollars
十亿美元
so that's to say
也就是说
the inland waterways
内河航道
effectively act as a massive subsidy
有效地充当巨额补贴
from the American taxpayer to its users
从美国纳税人到其用户
particularly to the agriculture industry
尤其是对农业
one could and some do argue that this is unfair
有人可能也有人确实认为这是不公平的
for everyone
对每个人来说
to pay for a system that only benefits the few
为一个只让少数人受益的系统买单
this argument is bolstered by the fact that
这一论点得到以下事实的支持
what these waterways are particularly good at
这些水道特别擅长什么
is getting bulk quantities of grain and soybean and
正在获得大量的谷物和大豆
other agricultural products to New Orleans
其他农产品到新奥尔良
to be transferred
待转移
onto an ocean going ship for international export
登上国际出口的远洋轮船
that's to say
也就是说
in extreme cases
在极端情况下
American taxpayers
美国纳税人
are paying
正在付款
to expand the profit margins of agribusinesses
扩大农业综合企业的利润率
selling their soybean to China
把他们的大豆卖给中国
this is true unlike roads
这是真的不像道路
there is no significant
没有显着的
direct utility for this transportation system
这个交通系统的直接效用
for the general public
面向公众
but right now
但是现在
the Mississippi is in this state where
密西西比河在这个州
it's extraordinarily expensive to run
运行起来非常昂贵
but it's also underfunded
但同时也资金不足
America does rely on it
美国确实依赖它
while some of its utility is enjoyed
虽然它的一些效用被享受
by all the foreign countries that buy American crops
所有购买美国作物的外国
it simultaneously secures the domestic food supply
同时保证了国内的食品供应
it transports raw materials
它运输原材料
that sit at the start of the supply chain
位于供应链的起点
for other industries
对于其他行业
in fact it's estimated that
事实上据估计
each day the river closes due to lock failure
河水每天都因船闸失灵而关闭
for example
例如
cost the American economy 300 million dollars
美国经济损失3亿美元
but despite that it's simultaneously under utilized
但尽管如此，它同时也没有得到充分利用。
far fewer barges traverse its stretch today
今天很少有驳船经过它的延伸
than in decades past
比过去几十年都多
as freight traffic has moved onto the rails and roads
随着货运转移到铁路和公路上
the rails
铁轨
and road systems are being stretched to their limits
道路系统已经达到极限
freight railroads are suffering from capacity shortages
货运铁路正遭受运力短缺
and fast deteriorating
并且迅速恶化
infrastructure
基础设施
due to their unwillingness to invest in capital
由于他们不愿投资资本
improvements while
改进
the trucking industry
货运业
is suffering from a driver shortage
正遭受司机短缺的困扰
as young people are unwilling to work
由于年轻人不愿意工作
in the increasingly
在日益
aged industry
老龄工业
there has been plenty of discussion
已经有很多讨论了
over developing a network of ports
过度发展港口网络
and vessels capable of transporting container cargo
和能够运输集装箱货物的船只
up and down the river
上上下下
so it can act as a direct competitor to freight
所以它可以作为运费的直接竞争对手
rail and trucks
铁路和卡车
but so far little has translated into action
但到目前为止，几乎没有转化为行动
the issues of inefficiency
效率低下的问题
and deterioration on the Mississippi
和密西西比河的恶化
are so well recognized
被如此广泛地认可
that barge operators themselves
驳船运营商自己
successfully advocated to be taxed more
成功主张多征税
they were the driving force behind the hike
他们是徒步旅行的驱动力
from 20 to 29 cents per gallon in 2014
2014年从每加仑20美分涨到29美分
because they so desperately wanted
因为他们非常想要
maintenance and upgrades
维护和升级
but it still wasn't even close to enough
但这还远远不够
right now the Mississippi
现在密西西比河
and America's other inland waterways
以及美国其他内陆水道
are funded and functional enough
资金充足且功能齐全
that they're relied on by whole industries
整个行业都依赖他们
and responsible for the economic ascent of entire
并负责整个经济的崛起
regions
地区
but not funded enough that they actually function
但没有足够的资金让它们真正发挥作用
even close to their full potential
甚至接近他们的全部潜力
that's to say
也就是说
they're great enough
他们已经足够好了
to have changed the entire course of American history
改变了整个美国历史的进程
but they're still just not great
但他们仍然不太好
one thing I noticed while researching this video
我在研究这段视频时注意到一件事
is that quite a few academics
那是相当多的学者吗？
have attempted to solve the issue of Mississippi River
试图解决密西西比河的问题
lock delays using data science
使用数据科学锁定延迟
after all even the busiest locks are used
毕竟即使是最繁忙的锁也被使用
well below their theoretical capacity
远低于他们的理论能力
but still experience delays
但仍然会遇到延迟
due to a lack of traffic management
由于缺乏交通管理
this is a great example of how knowledge in stem
这是一个很好的例子如何在干知识
subjects can help solve real world problems
受试者可以帮助解决现实世界的问题
and our sponsor brilliant
我们的赞助商才华横溢
is all about helping you gain a solid knowledge base
都是为了帮助你获得坚实的知识基础
in these topics
在这些主题中
in addition to data science
除了数据科学
they have all sorts of courses on subjects in math
他们有各种各样的数学课程
computer science and normal science
计算机科学和普通科学
I particularly liked their one
我特别喜欢他们的那个
on how large language models work
关于大型语言模型的工作原理
since you hear about LLMs like chatgbt
既然你听说了像chat gbt这样的LLM
all the time these days
这些天一直都是
so I think
所以我想
it's really important to understand
理解这一点真的很重要
how they actually work
它们实际上是如何工作的
I especially appreciate brilliant since to be honest
老实说，我特别欣赏辉煌
I struggled with stem subjects in formal education
我在正规教育中努力学习干细胞科目
yet their clear explanations
然而他们明确的解释
interactive exercises
互动练习
and useful graphics
和有用的图形
help you learn
帮助你学习
the intuitive fundamentals of each subject
每个学科的直觉基础
then as you go on
然后随着你的继续
they bring these fundamentals together
他们把这些基本要素结合在一起
into the larger subject
进入更大的主题
and suddenly you understand how say
突然间你明白了怎么说
neural networks work
神经网络工作
and brilliant also splits these subjects into small
和辉煌也把这些主题分成小
bite sized chunks that take no longer than 15 minutes
一口大小的大块，不超过15分钟
so it's super easy to make meaningful progress
所以取得有意义的进展非常容易
on learning the fundamentals of say
关于学习say的基础知识
calculus just while you're on the train
在火车上学习微积分
waiting at the doctor's office
在医生办公室等着
or in other small moments of your day
或者在你一天中的其他小时刻
when you might otherwise
当你可能不这样做的时候
just scroll through social media
只是滚动浏览社交媒体
brilliant has been one of our longest term sponsors
辉煌是我们长期赞助商之一
meaning
意义
plenty of Wendover viewers have found it worthwhile
很多温多弗的观众都觉得值得
and if you want to see why
如果你想知道为什么
you can try
你可以试试
everything brilliant has to offer for free for a full
一切辉煌都必须免费提供完整的
30 days when you visit brilliant
30天当你访问辉煌
org Wendover
组织文多弗
and you'll also get 20% off
您还可以享受20%的折扣
an annual premium subscription
年度保费认购